theleadmagnet.com 2019-06-06

# The Lead Magnet - Your #1 List Builder

**The Lead Magnet   Privacy Policy**

 **Content**

Content  
Scope and consent  
Controller  
Collection of personal data  
Use of personal data  
Disclosure of personal data  
Cookie, web beacons and similar technology  
Spam, spyware and identity theft are prohibited  
Access, review and change of your personal information  
Security and storage of personal data  
Closing your account and preserving personal information  
Your rights  
Contact Us

 **Scope and consent**

This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use, save, release and protect your personal information. It applies to the The Lead Magnet website and to all related websites, applications, services, and utilities where there is a reference to this Privacy Policy, no matter how you access or use them.

In this Privacy Policy, we use the term "personal data" to describe information that can directly or indirectly identify a natural person. We do not consider that personal data includes information that has been anonymized or aggregated in such a way that it can neither be used by other information or otherwise to identify a specific natural person.

By accepting this Privacy Policy, you agree that we may collect, use, disclose and save your personal information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. We may change this Privacy Policy with 30-day notice for existing users. We will post any changes on this page. In addition, we may inform you by email if there are major changes to this Privacy Policy.

**Third Party Sites:** Some pages on the The Lead Magnet website contain links to third party sites. These websites have their own privacy policies and The Lead Magnet is not responsible for their business, including but not limited to their information routines. Users who send information to or through these third-party websites should review the privacy policies for the websites before sending any personal data to them.

 **Controller**

The Lead Magnet, 76-15-9 Marina Bay, Jalan Tanjong Tokong, 104 70 Georgetown (hereinafter referred to as "The Lead Magnet") is personally responsible. The Lead Magnet is responsible for processing your personal information in accordance with the principles set forth in this Privacy Policy.

 **Collection of personal data**

If you use an account with us, you agree to share your personal information and agree that that information will be transferred and stored on our servers in Germany or elsewhere in the world, such as in the United States.

We collect the following types of information, including personal information, to allow you to use and access our websites, applications, services, and tools, to provide you with a personalized and better experience and more relevant content.

####  Information that we collect automatically

When you visit our sites, our applications, services, tools, or content clicks, we automatically collect information sent to us from your computer, mobile device, or other device that is used for access. This information can only be linked to you personally if you log in as a registered user and include: device ID or unique identifier, geographic location, type of device used, data and connection information, pageviews statistics, traffic to and from the websites, referrer URL , ad data, IP address and standard weblog information.

####  Information you provide to us

We may collect and store any information you provide on our websites or that you provide to us in connection with the use of our websites, applications, services or utilities. This includes:

  * Information you provide to us when registering an account, including e-mail address, phone number, mobile phone number and contact information;
  * transactional information based on your activities on the sites (such as what news you are interested in);
  * information provided in connection with discussions in forums, chats, dispute resolution, correspondence through our websites or correspondence sent to us; and

####  Information we collect from other sources

We may receive or collect additional information about you from third parties such as sales companies, data agencies and data providers and add it to our information about you. This may include demographic information and navigation information.

**Use of personal data**

Our purpose of collecting personal information is to access our websites, and / or to use our services, applications and tools, provide you with customer service and relevant information about your account and services, and provide you with a safe, hassle-free, efficient and custom experience. By accepting this Privacy Policy, you confirm that we may use your personal information to:

  * give you access to our websites, and the services and customer service you request;
  * prevent, detect and investigate fraud, security incidents and potentially prohibited or illegal activities;
  * customize, measure and improve our services, content and ads;
  * Contact you, either by email or by phone, to settle disputes, enter fees, resolve issues with your account or our websites, services, applications or tools, or for other purposes permitted by law;
  * compare information to verify accuracy and verify it with third parties;
  * inform and provide you with other services that you request and as described when we collect the information; and

  * for our legitimate interest:
    * handle our daily business needs; or
    * for monitoring and analysis purposes.

 **Disclosure of personal data**

We disclose personal data to comply with legal obligations, maintain our policies, respond to content requirements violating another's rights and protect third party rights, assets or security. Such information will only be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.

###  We may share your personal information with:

      * Group Company to provide common content and shared services for the detection and prevention of potentially illegal acts and violations of our policies, as well as providing guidance on their products, websites, applications, tools, services and communications in accordance with applicable law. Group companies may use this information to send marketing announcements only if you have consented to this and given your consent in such manner as to comply with applicable rules.
      * Subcontractors that help us conduct the business (such as but not limited to customer service, fraud investigations, invoice collection, loyalty programs, and site management).
      * Any third party to whom you explicitly wish us to send your information (or to any other third party to which you are informed and consent to the use of a particular service).
      * Supervisory authority, police authority or other authorized third party to answer questions in connection with a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity or other activity that may imply responsibility for us, you or other The Lead Magnet users. In such cases, as far as permitted by applicable law, we will disclose such information as is relevant and necessary for the investigation, such as name, social security number, city, state or province, postal address, telephone number, e-mail address, history of username and IP address.
      * Other companies if we would be merged or acquired by such company.
      * Other companies that offer an equivalent service or have a legitimate interest in accessing personal information to directly send you information that you are expected to have in accordance with your current service.
      * If your personal information will be used or disclosed for purposes other than those stated in this policy, we will inform you and, if applicable, request your consent.

###  Cookies, web beacons and similar technologies

When you visit or use our websites, services, applications, communication channels (such as email) and tools, we or our service providers may use cookies, web beacons, and similar technology to store information to provide you with a better, faster and safer experience and for advertising purposes. 

###  Spam, spyware and identity theft are prohibited

We and our users do not tolerate spam. To report The Lead Magnet-related spam or e-mail with a counterfeit sender or sender identity, please forward the email to theleadmagnet.com@gmail.com

We can automatically scan and manually filter messages to search for spam, viruses, phishing and other malicious activity or illegal or forbidden content, but we will not permanently save any messages sent through these tools.

###  Access, review and change of your personal information

Your registered e-mail address is the key to your user information. If you lose control of your email address, you lose your control of your personal information and may incur obligations for actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, you should immediately inform The Lead Magnet, if your e-mail address for some reason has come into the wrong hands.

###  Security and storage of personal data

We save and process your personal information on our servers in Germany and elsewhere in the world and undertake to provide appropriate protection for your personal information where such information is transferred to a location outside the EEA.

We use physical, technical and organizational security measures, in relation to the amount and sensitivity of personal data, to prevent unauthorized processing, including but not limited to unauthorized access, assignment and use, loss, erasure or damage to the user's personal data. Some of the security measures we use are firewalls, data encryption, login checks at our data centers, and permissions controls.

###  Closing your account and preserving personal information

At your request and in accordance with the provisions of this section, we will terminate your account and remove your personal information as soon as possible. Data deletion will be based on the type of account and in accordance with applicable law. We may also close or disable accounts that are not in use [.](http://info.tradera.com/sakerhetscenter/anvandaravtal/)

Typically, personal data attributable to closed or inactive accounts will be deleted or anonymized as soon as possible after the account has been closed or disabled. We may keep personal data attributable to closed accounts or accounts not used if:

      * We have a legitimate business interest and are not prohibited by law, such as collecting overdue fees, handling dispute resolution or
      * We are obliged to retain personal data to comply with legal obligations such as compliance with local laws, fraud and money laundering, or to take other actions permitted by law.

Under such circumstances, personal data will be handled safely and only for as long as necessary.

###  Your rights

Subject to the limitations of data protection legislation in the EEA, you have certain rights regarding your personal data. You are entitled to access, correction, limitation, objection, deletion and data portability. Please contact us if you wish to exercise any of these rights. If you wish to request access to any personal information we have about you, please note that photo identification will be required to prove your identity.

###  Contact Us

You can contact us at any time. If questions are not answered, please contact us by mail. 

[Our contact details](http://www.bequoted.com/om-bequoted/integritet/integritetspolicy/#) theleadmagnet.com@gmail.com, https://theleadmagnet.com/support

If you are not satisfied with how we handle your questions, you are entitled to file a complaint with the Data Protection Authority in your country.
